{
    "results" : [
    {
        "question":"4 + 2 = 7 ?",
        "correct": "1",
        "incorrect": ["true","eiei","eeee","eiei"]
        
    },
    {
        "question":"4 + 2 = 6 ?",
        "correct": "true",
        "incorrect": ["false"]
        
    },
    {
        "question":"1 + 2 = 3 ?",
        "correct": "true",
        "incorrect": ["false"]
        
    },
    {
        "question":"4 + 1 = 10 ?",
        "correct": "false",
        "incorrect": ["true"]
        
    },
    {
        "question":"4 + 2 = 7 ?",
        "correct": "1",
        "incorrect": ["true","eiei"]
        
    },
    {
        "question":"4 + 2 = 6 ?",
        "correct": "true",
        "incorrect": ["false"]
        
    },
    {
        "question":"1 + 2 = 3 ?",
        "correct": "true",
        "incorrect": ["false"]
        
    },
    {
        "question":"4 + 1 = 10 ?",
        "correct": "false",
        "incorrect": ["true"]
        
    },
    {
        "question":"4 + 2 = 6 ?",
        "correct": "true",
        "incorrect": ["false"]
        
    },
    {
        "question":"1 + 2 = 3 ?",
        "correct": "true",
        "incorrect": ["false"]
        
    },
    {
        "question":"4 + 1 = 10 ?",
        "correct": "false",
        "incorrect": ["true"]
        
    },
    {
        "question":"4 + 2 = 7 ?",
        "correct": "1",
        "incorrect": ["true","eiei"]
        
    },
    {
        "question":"4 + 2 = 6 ?",
        "correct": "true",
        "incorrect": ["false"]
        
    },
    {
        "question":"1 + 2 = 3 ?",
        "correct": "true",
        "incorrect": ["false"]
        
    },
    {
        "question":"4 + 1 = 10 ?",
        "correct": "false",
        "incorrect": ["true"]
        
    }]
   
}

